stuartweitzman.com 2018-10-05

# Privacy Policy | Shop Stuart Weitzman

###  PRIVACY POLICY

Welcome to www.stuartweitzman.com ("the Site"), the United States online store of STUART WEITZMAN® , which is operated by Coach Services, Inc (Coach Services, Inc and its affiliates, including Coach Services, Inc are hereinafter collectively referred to as "Stuart Weitzman".)

This privacy policy explains Stuart Weitzman’s information and data processing practices, as well as the choices you can make about the way your personal information or personally identifiable information (“PII”) is collected in Stuart Weitzman-owned and operated stores, on our social media platforms and via our Site, as well as the manner in which Stuart Weitzman will use your information.

By submitting your PII to Stuart Weitzman, you are agreeing that Stuart Weitzman may collect, store, use, disclose and destroy it in accordance with this policy. In this policy, we refer to the companies in our corporate group as "Stuart Weitzman", "we", or "us". We value every customer, prospective employee and employee and want you to trust our business and privacy practices. If you have any questions about the content of this policy, we encourage you to contact us as outlined below.

The information on this Site and our privacy policy are subject to change from time to time. Any material changes to our privacy policy and practices will be reflected on this page so that you can be aware of what information we collect and how we are using and/or disclosing it. By using our Site, you signify your consent to our privacy policy and consent to the collection and use of this information by Stuart Weitzman. If you do not agree to this privacy policy you may not access or otherwise use the Site.

PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOU

For purposes of this policy "personal information" / “personally identifiable information” / “PII” means any information by which you can be identified, including your name, address, telephone number, email address, billing and account information, credit or debit card information, and other information incidental to providing goods or services. In addition to collecting these types of PII, we may also collect your date of birth, product and lifestyle preferences, and other profile information to personalize your experience with us and to better serve you with our products and services.  We may ask you for your name, address, email address, social media user name/handle or other personal information when you post a photograph, enter or respond to a contest, survey, sweepstakes, or other promotional feature. Stuart Weitzman collects PII from you only when you voluntarily provide it to us.

Some examples of the manner in which we collect your PII include when you place an order through our Site or in our stores, create an online account on the Site, email registration, sweepstakes, contests, attend special events, create a wishlist, take a survey, contact us with a comment or question, sign up either online or in-store to receive emails or marketing communication about our products and services, or apply for a job with Stuart Weitzman. Some of these methods of data collection are further outlined below.

A. Site Registration

To become a registered member on our Site, you must complete the registration process by providing PII, including your first and last name and address, as well as information relating to what you would like to receive from us. If you decide to register, you will be asked to choose a password. You may also choose to provide your phone number, date of birth, and shoe preferences. When registered, you may choose to receive emails, SMS alerts, and request enrollment into a “Text-to-Buy” program.  You have the right to unsubscribe from marketing and these additional features at any time while you are signed-in to your account, or by contacting Customer Service, as described below.

B. Shopping With Stuart Weitzman

If you make a purchase from Stuart Weitzman, we obtain PII from you relating to the order. If you shop with us online or in-store, the PII collected by Stuart Weitzman will generally include your email, billing, shipping and payment information. You can also provide your mobile phone number to receive order updates and/or sale and event notifications. In addition to using this PII to fulfill your order, we also retain order information to better serve you on future purchases.

If you shop with us in-store, you may also be provided the option to fill out a “Preferred Customer Card” where you may also choose to provide your name, email, phone number, address, shoe size/width, and date of birth.  If you choose to opt in to receive text messages / participate in the “Text-to-Buy” feature, we will collect your initials. Completion of a Preferred Customer Card is optional.

Should you opt in to receive marketing communication from us we may also use this PII to contact you in connection with other Stuart Weitzman products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. Again, you may unsubscribe from marketing communication at any time. If you receive your marketing by email, each email will have a single click unsubscribe button at the bottom. If you receive your marketing by text, you can text STOP to 55855.

C. Employment Applications

If you apply for a job with Stuart Weitzman, PII requested may include your qualifications for the position, your education, applicable licenses or certifications, prior job history, references, and any other information that you may choose to include about yourself. If you submit a resume for general consideration or for a specific open position through our Site, we also request your name, address, phone number, email, whether or not you are a U.S. citizen, and your citizenship status.

If you are accepted for employment, we will, of course, collect other relevant PII from you and include it in your personnel file with that collected during the application process. The PII that will be collected for purposes of your employment includes your Social Security number.

D. Marketing Communications

If you choose to sign up for email communications either while browsing the Site or during one of your store visits, you must submit certain basic information during the registration process, which includes your name and email address. In some cases, the Site allows you to simply provide an email address. This PII is used to send you email marketing communications and to ensure that we can provide you with appropriate customer care and respond to your inquiries.

E. Product Reviews

While visiting certain portions of the Site, you may be given the opportunity to rate and provide a review on various Stuart Weitzman products. In order to fully participate in these portions of the Site, you will be asked to register with the Site or provide your email address which will be privately linked to your product ratings. Stuart Weitzman retains this additional PII, if provided, and uses it to help us better understand and respond to the collective feedback we receive. For any PII that we collect, Stuart Weitzman becomes the owner and data controller of that information.

F. Website Reviews

You may be asked to voluntarily provide feedback on the Site and provide your email address for us to contact you.  If you provide your email address after submitting your feedback, your email address will only be used to contact you with respect to your feedback and will not be added to our marketing list.

G. Customer Service

We collect certain PII (for example, your name and last name, phone number, and e-mail address) when you call or email Customer Service for assistance related to your use of the Site and/or the purchase of products on stuartweitzman.com. You may also choose to chat live with one of our customer service representatives. In order to respond to your question, you will be asked to provide your name and email address.

Our Customer Service agents may request additional personal data only in certain circumstances (your mailing address for special product orders, for example).

H. Information We Observe or Collect through Technology

Non-Personal Information

Like most websites, the server upon which this Site resides automatically collects non-personal information about your visit to this Site, such as your IP address, your computer type, your web browser type, operating system type and what pages linked you to this Site. An IP address is the number assigned to your computer when you connect to the Internet. This information is anonymous and does not contain your name, address, phone number, email address or other information that directly identifies you. We also may aggregate or anonymize PII so that it does not specifically identify you as an individual, and thereby turn it into non-personal information. If we link your non-personal information to your PII, then the combined set shall be treated as PII.

Cookies and Web Beacons

To better understand what you do while on our Site, we use a browser feature known as a cookie. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Among other things, cookies are used to do things like see how you navigate our Site, and remember you and your online purchases when you return. This helps us improve our site, provide better customer service, personalize your online experience, and personalize offers to you based on your unique tastes and purchase history.  
Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can change your browser so that it will not automatically accept cookies. Clearing cookies after each visit here will prevent observations from multiple sessions being aggregated over time. Please consider the consequences of blocking or clearing cookies. Many websites rely on their cookies to provide you with services or features that you have requested or expect.  
We also use web beacons (also known as clear gifs or pixel tags), which are small image files that we may place on web pages and within web-based email newsletters that we send. A web beacon is a nearly invisible pixel-sized graphic image on a web page, web-based document or e-mail message. It helps us do things like view the URL of the page on which the web beacon appears and the time our Site or email in question is viewed. Web beacons in emails help us confirm the receipt of, and response to, our emails, including those that you forward to friends and family; and they help deliver a more personalized online experience.  
Overall, these technologies may be used to help us see which of our interactive experiences online users like most. Cookies and web beacons also allow us to associate your online navigational or transactional information with any PII you provide. We’ll associate this information only for our purposes, including: to deliver products and services to you; to improve our business; to transact business; and to market our products and services through a variety of media like email, mobile advertising, and direct mail. As an example, we may use cookies to keep track of what you put into your shopping bag. That can help us contact you if your online session is disrupted in mid-purchase, resulting in an abandoned cart. We can also use this technology to determine whether you would be interested in participating in special events, given your preferences. The end result is a more personalized experience that is tailored to your needs and tastes.

I. Information Others Observe or Collect through Technology

Third-party service providers help us analyze our visitor's site and purchase preferences, and may help us deliver ads to you about our products through banner ads when you visit other websites (often referred to as "online network advertising"). The following provides more information about these service providers and the choices you have with respect to their services.

Third Party Cookies

Our Site contains cookies and similar devices from third party companies, such as analytics companies who help us better understand your use of our websites and for advertising purposes, as described below. They accomplish this by using some or all of the technologies described in Information We Observe or Collect Through Technology.

Advertising

We contract with third-party advertising companies that, in turn, collect anonymous, non-personally identifying information by placing cookies on your browser when you visit us here. This form of advertising is called "behavioral advertising" and we believe that such advertising is a benefit to you because you will see advertisements that are relevant to your interest. These companies may use information about your visit to deliver our ads on this and other web sites through their online advertising networks. These companies also provide this information to us which we, in turn, use to gauge how effective our ads are. If you want more information about such advertising or if you would like to opt-out of such targeting by certain companies, you can exercise such choices by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance (<http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>) and Network Advertising Initiative (<http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>) (you will leave this Site for a centrally managed online site where you can specify your preference). We comply with the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising.

Do Not Track

We do not respond to or honor "do not track" (a/k/a DNT) signals or similar mechanisms transmitted by web browsers.

J. Social Media Platforms

This site provides you with the ability to register, log into, "like" or otherwise interact with your social media services, including, but not limited to, Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, Pinterest, WeChat, Weibo, Youku, Vine, and other social media services.

These features may enable integration and/or access to your social media accounts. We do not control these social media services or your profiles on these services, and we do not establish privacy settings or rules for how your PII on those services will be used. Your information will be subject to the applicable social media service’s terms and conditions and your current privacy settings on such social media service. You are encouraged to read all policies and information regarding the applicable social media services to learn more about how they handle your information. By accessing any social media service, you will be assuming the risk that the information you provide on that service may be viewed and/or used by third parties for any purpose. You agree that we are not responsible for any acts or omissions by these social media service providers.

STUART WEITZMAN’S USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We use PII collected from you for the following purposes:

·         to provide customer service or respond to a request;

·         to improve the content, appearance and utility of our Site or stores;

·         to understand your needs and preferences in relation to Stuart Weitzman;

·         to develop, market, sell or provide products and services;

·         to conduct surveys, research and evaluations;

·         to manage and develop our business and operations, administer accounts, and collect and process payments;

·         to detect and protect us and other third parties against negligence, fraud, theft and other illegal activities;

·         as permitted by, and to comply with, any legal or regulatory requirements, process or provisions; and

·         if you submit a resume, we may use the information you provide solely for the purpose of evaluating you as a candidate for employment and to contact you about prospective employment.

We may combine information you provide to us from multiple sources and with information from third parties including demographic or public information.

STUART WEITZMAN’S SHARING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We may share your PII with our subsidiaries or affiliated companies, including those located in other countries. We also may share your PII with selected third parties who provide services to us, including to help handle parts of our business because of their expertise, resources, or scale. They help us do things like fulfill orders, process payments, monitor site activity, maintain databases, administer and monitor emails, respond to customer service inquiries, fulfill unsubscribe requests, administer and send mobile messages, and provide consulting services. We may work with third parties and provide them with access to your PII so that they may enhance our databases or help us to deliver behavioral advertising content to you across other websites as described above in the "Advertising" section.

Such third parties may have access to, store and process your PII to provide services on our behalf, which may occur in the United States or in countries outside of the United States. Our service providers are not authorized to use your PII for any purpose other than to provide the services that Stuart Weitzman has contracted from them.

Law Enforcement

We also must always reserve the right to disclose PII about you as required by law, in response to legal process including law enforcement requests, and where needed to protect the safety, property, or legal rights of Stuart Weitzman or its affiliates or third parties.

Third Party Sites

Occasionally we may provide a link to a third party website, which is not owned or operated by Stuart Weitzman. If you elect to provide your PII on that third party website, this information will be subject to that third party website's privacy policy and security practices. We are not responsible or liable for any content presented by or contained on any independent website, including, but not limited to, any advertising claims or marketing practices. We also are not responsible or liable for any privacy or security policies of these third party sites.

Successor in Business

We reserve the right to transfer your PII and other information to our successors in business or divisions and purchasers of our assets.

Transfers of PII to the U.S.

[www.stuartweitzman.com](http://www.stuartweitzman.com/) is primarily intended for residents of the U.S. Irrespective of where you're located when you access it, browse it and interact with it, if you use this Site and provide personal information to Stuart Weitzman as described in the PERSONAL DATA WE COLLECT FROM YOU section of this policy, such personal data about you may be transferred to Stuart Weitzman in the U.S.  Please note that there may be different standards that apply to how your data is used and protected than the standards in place in your country.

YOUR INFORMATION — YOUR RIGHTS

A. Right to Unsubscribe

You have the right to unsubscribe from receiving marketing communications from Stuart Weitzman, as well as the right to unsubscribe from any of the programs that we offer. To unsubscribe from our marketing emails, click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any Stuart Weitzman email that you receive, visit our _[Email Preferences](http://www.stuartweitzman.com/optout/)_ page, email us at [service@stuartweitzman.com](mailto:service@stuartweitzman.com) with your request, or call customer care at 1.877.793.4896.  This will stop future email offers from us, but won't stop operational or transactional messages such as email confirmations of your online orders, or customer service communications. If you receive communications directly from Stuart Weitzman store associates and would like to opt-out, simply reply to the store associate’s email or text message with your unsubscribe request.  You can also email [service@stuartweitzman.com](mailto:service@stuartweitzman.com) or visit any Stuart Weitzman store with your opt-out request from communications received directly from store associates.

Please note that if you already have requested products or services when you decide to withdraw consent, there may be a short period of time for us to update your preferences and ensure that we honor your request.

B. Update, Modify or Correct Your Personal Information

The accuracy, integrity and security of your PII are very important and Stuart Weitzman takes reasonable steps to ensure that these priorities are addressed. We encourage you to contact us to update or correct your PII if it changes or if you believe that any information that we have collected about you is inaccurate.

You can also review and change certain PII related to your use of this Site (such as your name and contact information). To access your information on this Site, simply sign in to your account using your email address and password, and you will be able to edit your PII in your account profile.

Consistent with legal requirements and limitations, Stuart Weitzman also permits you to obtain a copy of PII that we hold about you. To do so, please use the contact information in the Questions or Concerns section of this privacy policy. Please note that we will likely require additional information from you in order to honor your request, such as to ensure proper authentication or to verify the business branch of Stuart Weitzman to which the information was provided.

C. Safeguarding Your Information

Stuart Weitzman follows applicable laws and requirements to protect and safeguard your PII. We have adopted physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards that are designed to protect your PII, by reducing the risk of loss, misuse, alteration, theft, unauthorized access, or unauthorized disclosure.

For example, when you place an order on our Site, we use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology, an encryption tool that provides security while transmitting information over the Internet. We also use firewall technology, password controls, and other technological and procedural safeguards in respect of your online interactions with Stuart Weitzman.

We evaluate our privacy safeguards on an ongoing basis to help minimize risks from new security threats as they become known. Although we have implemented the above security measures, we note that 100% guaranteed security is not possible for any company.

D. California Residents

Under California law, if you are a resident of California, you may make a written request to Stuart Weitzman about how we have shared your information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the immediately prior calendar year. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [service@stuartweitzman.com](mailto:service@stuartweitzman.com). You must include your full name, e-mail address, and postal address in your message. In response to your written request, Stuart Weitzman is allowed to provide you with a notice describing the cost-free means to opt-out of our sharing your information with third parties with whom Stuart Weitzman does not share the same brand name, if the third party will use it for their direct marketing purposes.

VISITORS FROM OUTSIDE THE U.S.

stuartweitzman.com is maintained in the United States. This privacy policy governs the information collected at this Site irrespective of where you're located when you access it, browse it and interact with it. This means your PII may be stored outside of the province, state, and/or country in which you reside, and processed by us, an affiliate or a third-party service provider as described in this privacy policy. You freely and specifically consent to such transfer of your PII. Moreover, governmental bodies that have jurisdiction (e.g., courts and law enforcement agencies) may be entitled to access your PII.

Stuart Weitzman authorizes transfers of personal information from European Union and Switzerland to the United States using European Commission-approved Standard Contractual Clauses (also referred to as Model Contracts).

INTERNATIONAL STUART WEITZMAN SITES

Based on the shipping destination you select on any of our Sites, we will automatically redirect you to the official Stuart Weitzman Site nearest to that country. Please be aware that once you are redirected, you will be subject to the privacy policy of that site.

OUR COMMITMENT TO CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

This Site is not intended for use by children under the age of 13. Stuart Weitzman does not knowingly register or otherwise collect PII from any person under the age of 13. If we become aware that a person under the age of 13 has provided us with PII, we will use all reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database.

QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS

For questions about our privacy policy, you can contact us at:

Email: [service@stuartweitzman.com](mailto:service@stuartweitzman.com)

Phone: 1.877.793.4896

Mail:  
Stuart Weitzman Customer Services  
10 Hudson Yards, Floor 18  
New York, NY 10001

When contacting us, please be sure to provide us with your a correct contact information in order to be sure we handle your request correctly.

Following any incidence of communication from you to Stuart Weitzman some of your PII may be retained for a period of time for financial, legal or technical reasons.

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

This privacy policy replaces all previous disclosures we may have provided you about our information practices associated with the Site. Stuart Weitzman reserves the right, at its discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this privacy policy at any time. You should check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this privacy policy will be considered your consent to those changes.

Also, please note that the examples contained in this privacy policy are illustrations only and are not intended to be exhaustive.

Updated: January 19, 2017
